<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Atlanta New Horizons Band</title><link>https://atlantanewhorizonsband.org/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Atlanta New Horizons Band</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 13:55:19 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://atlantanewhorizonsband.org/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. Army Field Band - Jazz Ambassadors</title><link>https://atlantanewhorizonsband.org/post/us-army-field-band/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 13:55:19 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://atlantanewhorizonsband.org/post/us-army-field-band/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="attention--this-performance-has-been-cancelled"&gt;ATTENTION: This Performance Has Been Cancelled&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Army Jazz Ambassadors, the premier touring ensemble of the United States Army, bring their world-class musicianship to the Rialto for a free evening of patriotic and jazz favorites. Formed in 1969, this 19-member big band is renowned for its dynamic arrangements and performances that span a range of styles, including swing, bebop, Latin jazz, and more.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Musicians Wanted for Adult Concert Band</title><link>https://atlantanewhorizonsband.org/post/musicians-wanted/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atlantanewhorizonsband.org/post/musicians-wanted/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="img/MusiciansWanted.png" alt="Musicians Wanted" title="Musicians Wanted for Adult Band"&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The ATLANTA NEW HORIZONS BAND, founded in April 1999, provides opportunities for adults to play music again after they had been active in school programs and then inactive for a long period. Music playing may also have been interrupted due to professional or other life circumstances.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ANHB wants to invite these folks to renew their interest and passion. Now may be the time of life when you have the chance to devote it to music. We perform at a variety of venues such as churches, retirement homes, festivals and more. We are welcoming players for all sections with the ability to read music.
For more information, send us a messsage. &lt;div class="contactform_div"&gt;
 

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;form
 action="https://formspree.io/f/xrbqlkjq"
 method="POST"
&gt;
 &lt;label&gt;
 Your email:
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;input type="email" name="email"&gt;
 &lt;/label&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;label&gt;
 Your message:
 &lt;textarea name="message"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;
 &lt;/label&gt;
 
 &lt;button type="submit"&gt;Send&lt;/button&gt;
&lt;/form&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Black Horse Troop March</title><link>https://atlantanewhorizonsband.org/post/black-horse-troop-march/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 13:55:19 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://atlantanewhorizonsband.org/post/black-horse-troop-march/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Composed in 1924, John Philip Sousa&amp;rsquo;s Black Horse Troop March is a vibrant tribute to the U.S. Army’s 3rd Cavalry Regiment, known as the &amp;ldquo;Black Horse Troop.&amp;rdquo; Written for their annual dinner, this march captures Sousa’s signature flair with bold brass, lively rhythms, and a spirited melody. Its galloping tempo evokes the energy of cavalry on the move, making it a favorite among bands and audiences. Check out a performance to feel the patriotic pulse of this American classic!&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Jenn Ambrosiano</title><link>https://atlantanewhorizonsband.org/post/jenn-ambrosiano/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 13:53:04 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://atlantanewhorizonsband.org/post/jenn-ambrosiano/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;In our twenty-ninth AME Podcast, we continue our quest to serve artistic excellence through a conversation with Jenn Ambrosiano, flutist, teacher, repairwomen, and community band founder. Jenn, who was encouraged to participate with music from the excitement of her father during her public-school years and beyond, has become a strong advocate for community music.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>